Candice Weaver

Website: candiceweaver.dev

### SUMMARY

As a dedicated and self-motivated Front End Developer with over 2 years of professional experience, I am enthusiastic about pushing the boundaries of web and app development. My proficiency in JavaScript, TypeScript, React, NextJS, and React Native empowers me to create exceptional digital experiences. I am deeply committed to continuous learning and eager to contribute my skills and passion to a dynamic team, driving innovation and excellence in the world of web and app development. Seeking opportunities for career growth and advancement in this exciting field.

# COMPUTER SKILLS

# Languages

- Proficient in: HTML5; CSS3; JavaScript; TypeScript; React; NextJS; React Native
- Familiar with: Firebase

### Software

- Proficient in: Git/GitHub; Visual Studio Code; Xcode; Android Studio
- Familiar with: Linux; WordPress

### **EXPERIENCE**

**Developer** Jan 2022 – Present

Si digital

- Primary role is to build & maintain websites and apps for clients
- Actively participate in meetings with clients and colleagues
- Some experience leading the development of a React Native app

# Junior Web Developer

Sept 2021 - Jan 2022

StoneSpiral Ltd

- Primary role was to continue to develop programming skills
- Gained experience building websites for clients
- · Communicated regularly with other team members remotely

# **Business Development Specialist**

April 2021 - June 2021

# Astute

- Primary responsibilities included selling digital solutions to existing customers
- Communicated effectively with customers over the phones
- Understood the customers' needs to match them with a suitable product

# **EDUCATION**

# The Open University Computing and IT The Open University Business Management – Certificate of Higher Education Brockenhurst College 2 x AS Levels and 2 x A Levels Highcliffe Secondary School 13 x GCSEs Oct 2021 – Present Feb 2019 – May 2021 Sep 2014 – July 2016 Sep 2014 – July 2016

### REFERENCES AVAILABLE ON REQUEST